<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title xml:lang="fr">Mentions légales</title>
            <title xml:lang="en">Terms and conditions</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Publication information</p>        
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Information about the source</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
     <body xml:id="static">
        <div xml:lang="fr">
           <head type="static_main_title">Mentions légales</head>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Éditeur du site web</head>
              <p>Institut d'histoire de la Réformation 
                 <lb/>Université de Genève, Bâtiment des Philosophes
                 <lb/>Boulevard des Philosophes 22
                 <lb/>CH-1211 Genève 4
              </p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Directrice de publication</head>
              <p>Mme Daniela Solfaroli Camillocci – Professeure (Institut d’histoire de la Réformation)</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Hébergement du site web</head>
              <p>Institut d'histoire de la Réformation</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Webmaster</head>
              <p>Mme Elina LEBLANC – Collaboratrice scientifique (Faculté des lettres de l'Université de Genève)</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Utilisation des images</head>
              <p>Les modalités d’utilisation et de diffusion des images sont définies par les bibliothèques qui conservent les imprimés. Nous invitons les utilisateurs à se référer aux notices de chaque édition pour prendre connaissance de la licence appliquée (dans la rubrique « Métadonnées »).</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Utilisation des éditions et des métadonnées</head>
              <p>L’utilisation des éditions et des métadonnées est protégée par la licence Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY 4.0). La source des données doit être indiquée selon les modalités décrites dans la page <ref type="static_link" target="https://setaf.unige.ch/static/comment-citer">Comment citer</ref>.</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Mises à jour</head>
              <p>Le projet SETAF met tout en œuvre pour assurer l’exactitude des informations diffusées sur son site à la date de leur mise en ligne, ainsi que leur mise à jour régulière. Cependant, nous ne garantissons pas l’absence d’omissions ou d’erreurs et vous remercions par avance pour vos retours et suggestions permettant d’enrichir les données diffusées. La bibliothèque numérique se réserve le droit de modifier, à tout moment et sans préavis, le contenu du site Web.</p>
              <p>Dernière mise à jour des mentions légales : 17/09/2025</p>
           </div>
        </div>
        
        <div xml:lang="en">
           <head type="static_main_title">Terms and conditions</head>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Website’s publisher</head>
              <p>Institut d'histoire de la Réformation 
                 <lb/>Université de Genève, Bâtiment des Philosophes
                 <lb/>Boulevard des Philosophes 22
                 <lb/>CH-1211 Genève 4
              </p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Publication editor</head>
              <p>Mme Daniela Solfaroli Camillocci – Professor (Institut d’histoire de la Réformation)</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Hosting</head>
              <p>Institut d'histoire de la Réformation</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Webmaster</head>
              <p>Mme Elina LEBLANC – Scientific collaborator (Faculté des lettres de l'Université de Genève)</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Use of images</head>
              <p>The terms of use and circulation of the images are defined by the libraries that hold the documents. We invite users to refer to the notices for each edition to find out the licence used (in the ‘Metadata’ section).</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Use of editions and metadata</head>
              <p>The use of the editions and metadata is protected by the Creative Commons Attribution licence (CC BY 4.0). The source of the data must be indicated as described on the <ref type="static_link" target="https://setaf.unige.ch/static/comment-citer">How to cite page</ref>.</p>
           </div>
           
           <div>
              <head type="static_subtitle">Updates</head>
              <p>The project SETAF makes every effort to ensure that the information on its website is accurate at the time it is put online, and that it is regularly updated. However, we do not guarantee the absence of omissions or errors, and we thank you in advance for your feedback and suggestions to enrich the data provided. The project reserves the right to modify the content of the website at any time and without prior notice.</p>
              <p>Last update of terms and conditions: 17/09/2025</p>
           </div>
        </div>
     </body>
  </text>
</TEI>